JAIME DYBUNCIO

jaimedybuncio@gmail.com | (818) 618-4562 | San Francisco, CA | LinkedIn | GitHub

PROFESSIONAL OVERVIEW

I have 6 years of experience working on Business Operations and Analytics teams where I learned to balance building process quality with speed. Currently, I am a Data Science Immersive student at Galvanize due to my desire to consistently grow in the ways I can offer more insight and be more impactful. Seeking opportunities in which I can enable smarter decision making and play a decisive role in helping a company achieve its mission.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

GALVANIZE DATA SCIENCE IMMERSIVE PROGRAM

San Francisco, CA Jan 2020 - Jun 2020

• A 700+ hour data science immersive training program covering core data science areas including probability and statistics, databases, regression, supervised and unsupervised machine learning algorithms, and NLP.

FIVESTARS LOYALTY
Director of Business Operations
Business Operations Manager
Senior Sales Analyst

San Francisco, CA Feb 2019 - Dec 2019

Feb 2018 - Jan 2019 Mar 2016 - Jan 2018

- Cross-Functional Bridge: Regularly presented in front of and worked with business and product leaders. Articulated the cost and the benefit of certain strategic ideas. Played a key role in the transition of over 50 sales, support, marketing, and account management jobs from San Francisco and Denver to an El Paso office.
- Forecasting & Modeling: Built the board-facing monthly recurring revenue model which was used to project net bookings and processing volumes. This included projecting headcount, marketing lead, sales funnel, and churn performance. Met with directors monthly to compare actuals against the model to highlight priorities.
- Source of Truth Reporting: Created core data model for all business units which served as the basis for our official numbers. Used Treasure Data and SQL to create the core data tables and used Tableau for dashboards...

CREDIT SESAMESan Francisco, CASenior Marketing Data AnalystJan 2016 - Mar 2016Marketing Operations AnalystJul 2015 - Dec 2015

• Advanced Analytics: Led strategy shift from acquiring customers at the lowest cost to optimizing ROI which led to a 100% improvement in our LTV:CPA ratio when comparing July to December 2015's customer cohorts. Created visibility into the revenue collected over time by grouping customer cohorts across multiple variables.

RED VENTURES

Sales Operations Associate

Indian Land, SC
Sep 2013- Dec 2014

• Properly Trained: Learned core Sales and Business Operations skills from an industry standard company.

PROJECTS

- Increasing Fivestars' Customer LTV (2017- launched Jan 2018)
- Used logistic regression to identify contract related variables associated with higher customer retention.
- Created a new sales compensation plan which incentivized the identified deal quality levers.
- Got executive sign-off and launched the new commission plan along with new KPIs across the entire sales team
- Saw customer 1 yr LTV increase by over \$150 when comparing 2018 vs. 2017 cohorts...

TECHNICAL/PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: Python & SQL

Software Tools: Tableau, Treasure Data, & Salesforce

EDUCATION

DAVIDSON COLLEGE

Davidson, NC

Bachelor of Arts in Economics, 2013

• Graduated with Honors and was Magna Cum Laude